---
- 
  question: "How do I volunteer?"
  answer: 
        "Want to get involved and join the team of beautiful volunteers that make Brainchild possible?
        Volunteering at Brainchild festival will mainly be a stewarding role. For example helping to set up the festival site, attending the car park, litter picking or bar work. They may also be other opportunities during set up to help construct in a more creative manner.
        

        The volunteer system works with a ticket bond, you help out with two 3 hour shifts and one 4 hour shift and then get half of your ticket cost back at the end of the festival. Some shift patterns will start on the Thursday to help set up, if you choose to do this you get an extra day on site and then more time to enjoy your weekend. Likewise, some will end on the Monday, meaning you work less over the course of the weekend.
        

        The volunteer team is brilliant to be a part of and we will try our best to put you on jobs with your friends if they volunteer too. Volunteers are an important part of Brainchild as without them the festival would not be the amazing event that it is. Therefore to show our love you are all invited to the staff party on Monday evening after the pack down to celebrate another magnificent Brainchild.



        So dont hesitate to buy your volunteer ticket and jump on board. We would love for you to join the crew and make Brainchild 2015 truly spectacular.
        If you have any questions please email **tomo@brainchildfestival.co.uk**"
-
  question: "Where is the festival and how do I get there?"
  answer: 
    "We’re running in the fields and woods of Bentley Wildfowl and Motor Museum, Halland, East Sussex, BN8 5AF.
    There *is* even a mini railway to take you on a tour round the site!


    
    Getting here by train: Nearest stations are Uckfield and Lewes. London Bridge to Uckfield is 1hr 10 minutes, and Brighton to Lewes is 15 minutes. 



    Getting here by car: 30 minutes from Brighton via A27 & A26, 60-90 minutes from London via A22."
-
  question: "Whats the deal with camping?"
  answer: 
    "We’ve got a big campsite right next to the main festival area, none of the hours of walking that you have to do at big festivals! The camping area is big enough for everyone at the festival to camp together. All you need to do is bring your tent. Please bear in mind we can’t have campervans or campfires at the festival."
-
  question: "What should I bring with me?"
  answer: 
    "Essentials: your ticket and some valid ID. Brainchild is an 18+ festival and you will need this and your ticket to get your wristband and gain entry.


    
    Please do bring: things that will help you gain from the festival, so notebooks, yoga mats, cameras, instruments for the jams…
    


    Please **dont** bring any glass, fireworks or illegal substances. We have a zero tolerance approach to illegal drugs and legal highs."
-
  question: "Will there be showers?"
  answer: 
    "Yes! We'll have more showers this year, so bring your towels and washing stuff if you want to use them."
-
  question: "How much alcohol can I bring?"
  answer: 
    "All alcohol must be decanted into plastic bottles - we have a strict no glass rule on site. Per person, alcohol is limited to either: a 70cl bottle of spirits, OR one crate of beer/cider/ale OR two bottles of wine. Alcohol can only be brought in on first entry."
-
  question: "Is the festival family friendly?"
  answer: 
    "Brainchild is an 18+ festival, so we can’t allow kids on site. Sorry!"
-
  question: "How do you cater for disabilities?"
  answer: 
    "Please get in touch with us about any requirements that you have and we can arrange priority parking spaces, camping and stage seating."
-
  question: "When does the festival start and finish?"
  answer: 
    "Gates open at 12:00 on Friday 10th July, with acts beginning shortly afterwards - the sooner you can get on site the better! The gates close again around 12:00 on Monday 13th July."
-
  question: "What is there to eat?"
  answer: 
    "We will have a great catering tent, open all hours and providing many options for breakfast, lunch and dinner throughout the festival. More details about our menus will be published nearer to the event."